<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Macchiatobin - tag - Jason DeTiberus</title><link>http://detiber.github.io/tags/macchiatobin/</link><description>Macchiatobin - tag - Jason DeTiberus</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 14:27:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://detiber.github.io/tags/macchiatobin/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Properly configuring network devices on a Macchiatobin</title><link>http://detiber.github.io/posts/macchiatobin_network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 14:27:00 -0500</pubDate><author/><guid>http://detiber.github.io/posts/macchiatobin_network/</guid><description>I recently broke out as Macchiatobin that I had laying around from a few years ago for testing arm64 support with Tinkerbell. I started with getting an updated version of EDK2 running on it. Followed by getting an updated version of mainline u-boot running on it. It was during the process of running a newer version of u-boot that I realized I never properly configured this board after getting it.</description></item><item><title>Current u-boot on a Macchiatobin</title><link>http://detiber.github.io/posts/macchiatobin_uboot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 15:40:00 -0500</pubDate><author/><guid>http://detiber.github.io/posts/macchiatobin_uboot/</guid><description>I recently broke out as Macchiatobin that I had laying around from a few years ago for testing arm64 support with Tinkerbell. I started with getting an updated version of EDK2 running on it. While the UEFI firmware was working well, it didn&amp;rsquo;t give me the ability to override the MAC addresses for the interfaces, which caused issues after the board booted into Linux, where a random MAC address was generated for each interface.</description></item><item><title>UEFI on a Macchiatobin</title><link>http://detiber.github.io/posts/macchiatobin_uefi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 12:38:46 -0500</pubDate><author/><guid>http://detiber.github.io/posts/macchiatobin_uefi/</guid><description>I recently broke out as Macchiatobin that I had laying around from a few years ago for testing arm64 support with Tinkerbell. Revisiting the wiki it was obvious that the instructions for building the UEFI support was pretty outdated and I wanted to try and use primarily upstream sources rather than the forked and unmaintained versions used in the wiki.
Prerequisites You will need all the software dependencies listed in http://wiki.</description></item></channel></rss>